You have done well, worthy of my trust.
Everything is going according to plan.
I am about to be betrothed to Lady Rinkham.
Once that is done, I will be able to get close to Luang Witsanu.
Then all that is left is to bide our time
until you gain the power to rule this city.
Dad, there is something I think you should know.
The guard protecting the lady is not a man.
it’s a woman in disguise.
Once I get rid of that guard, everything will be much easier.
That fool Luang Witsanu even cast her aside himself.
Then proceed with the plan at once.
We must not waste time.
Congratulations to you both on your successful engagement.
From this day forward, I ask that you take good care of each other.
I look forward to the day you two share the wedding chamber together in the near future.
Rinkham...
Rinkham!
Dad, wait here a moment.
I shall fetch some water for you.
Put this slow-acting poison into Luang Witsanu's meal.
It will kill him slowly and silently,
without anyone suspecting a thing.
And when he can no longer bear it...
...I shall step in to rule the city as his son-in-law!
The time is near,
Luang Witsanu, you fool
Kaew, you promised you would stay with me forever.
Where are you now?
Why must you leave me to face these troubles all alone?
I am sorry for everything.
I am so sorry I couldn't keep my promise.
1 week later
Take it easy, Dad.
I will help take care of the kingdom's affairs on the days you aren't up to it.
I can handle it.
I’ve been by Dad’s side all along.
I know what needs to be done.
Ruling a kingdom isn't a game, Rinkham.
As a woman, you shouldn't get involved.
Are you still thinking about her?
I always think about her.
And the other day, you went there, didn't you?
To her engagement ceremony.
I went, but she didn't see me.
I just stood and watched from afar.
I promised to take care of her,
to protect her.
But I couldn't keep my promise.
I was thrown out like I was worthless—
without even the right to stand by her side.
She is in a dangerous place,
yet here I am...
Dad!
Hang in there.
Here’s some water.
Rest for a bit, Dad.
I’ll go boil some medicine for you.
There’s only one pack left.
I’ll go boil the medicine myself.
You go buy some more.
But... I don't have enough money left to buy medicine for my dad.
Go
Ming..
I have some savings left.
Take it.
I really want to help you.
Thank you, Ming.
Go buy the medicine and keep it.
I’ll look after your dad for you.
Do you have slow-acting poison?
Yes, I do.
Do you have any more?
Thank you!
Excuse me, uncle.
Yes?
What kind of medicine did that nobleman buy just now?
slow-acting poison
slow-acting poison?
You promised you would protect me forever...
So where are you now?